http://www.asahiagency.com/privacy/

Basic Policy
Asahi Agency considers that the protection of customers' personal information is a material social responsibility, as well as a legal obligation. Our company hereby prescribes the privacy policy as set out below in order to respect and protect customers' rights regarding their personal information.
Use of Personal Information
When Asahi Agency obtains personal data from customers and clients, we appropriately manage the Personal Information and use it properly in accordance with its goals.
Disclosure of Personal Information to a third party
Asahi Agency executes proper management of personal information and shall not provide any third parties with such information without prior permission from the customer or any other persons representing themselves. However, the following cases are excepted.
Cases based on the law.
Cases where the protection of a person's life, health, or assets are on the line and the person is question cannot be contacted for permission.
Cases where improvement of public health or the implementation of sound nurturing of juveniles is involved and the person is question cannot be contacted for permission.
Cases of co-operation with national agencies or local public bodies, or else bodies entrusted with the business of executing the law, in which obtaining the permission of the person involved may constitute an obstruction of the aforementioned.
Information update and notice
Asahi Agency may change to this Policy without notice. Before you use the service provided by this Site, please read the latest notice at this Site first.
Contact
You ever have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
Asahi Agency
33F ARK Mori Bldg., 1-12-32 Akasaka, Minato-ku Tokyo, JAPAN 107-6033
TEL: +81-(0)3-5574-7890 / FAX: +81-(0)3-5574-7887
